It's time for Enjoy Simple English
森崎ウィンです
今月からはですね
2024年の4月から9月に放送した内容を
再放送でお送りします
毎週月曜日はオリジナルのショートストーリー
今日お届けするのは
ウォーキング
健康を気遣ってウォーキングを始めるお父さんですが
なぜか娘がそんなお父さんに
呆れてしまうという内容です
なぜなのでしょう
Let's listen
お父さん、どこにいますか?
私は部屋にいます、カナコ。
私は着替えをしています。
今日は土曜日です。
今日、お仕事はしないのですか?
No, but my health check-up results weren't too good.
So my doctor told me I have to exercise more.
So?
So? See?
Tada!
I'm going to go walking on my days off.
did you buy those new clothes just for walking?
Yes. See you later.
Wait, Dad. You've never been able to continue any kind of exercise.
You have tried fishing, tennis, golf, and even squash.
Oh, this will be different. It's just walking.
So, where are you going to walk?
I have it all planned.
I'm going to walk through the town.
Dad, are those new sneakers?
Aren't they cool?
See you later!
I wish she wouldn't treat me like a child.
I was all excited, but not anymore.
Well, I'm going to take a deep breath and start walking.
Here we go!
うーん、実は思ったよりも楽しいですね。
この道を歩いているときは、 チェリートリーを見つけたことがありませんでした。
いつもこの道を歩いているのですが、 何か違いがあるようです。
これは良いですね。
あ、それは何ですか?
私はこの焼肉店を見たことがありませんでした。
こんにちは。今日開かれました。
ん〜 新鮮な焼きたての匂いはとても美味しい!
時間があれば、どうぞ入って来て下さい!
色んな種類のたくさんのたくさんのたくさんのたくさんのたくさんのたくさんが入って来てくれます!
私はそう思います!
お父さんはとても遅いです。
彼はどこにいるの?
私は電話をかけて電話をかけて、でも、彼は答えないのです。
だから、母は私が彼を探してみてくれました。
私はどうして?
I'm fit, so I don't have to exercise.
Wait, is that dad at the sweets shop?
Here you go, sir.
A cup of green tea and a taiyaki.
Thank you.
I never knew there was a sweets shop here.
Did you open recently?
No, we've been here for a long time now.
About 80 years.
Really?
私の近郊に何か知らないことがあったのです。
このタイヤキはとても美味しいです。
歩きはとても楽しいです。
失礼します。もう一つのタイヤキをいただけますか?
パパ!
カナコ?
何をしているの?
それは私の質問です、パパ。
I'm eating Taiyaki, can't you see?
By the way, do you know about this shop?
Dad, I thought you went on a walk to exercise.
Um, I'm walking and having breakfast.
I'm killing two birds with one stone, right?
皆さんこのショートストーリー覚えてましたか
I'm killing two birds with one stone
日本語だと一石二鳥
すごく短いのに英語だとすごく長くなる
でもその代わりすごくシンプルで覚えやすい
そんな印象僕は受けました
そしてHealth Checkup
健康診断行かないとな
それではまた明日もお会いしましょう
See you tomorrow